Guide to the Yale College Student Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Grade lists and grade change records, 1901-1996; Accession 2004-A-073
  - 1993 Spring A - R (Box 79)
  - 1993 Spring S - Z (Box 80)
  - 1993 Fall (Box 80)
  - 1994 Spring A - P (Box 81)
  - 1994 Spring R - Z (Box 82)
  - 1994 Fall (Box 82)
  - 1995 Spring A - R (Box 83)
  - 1995 Spring S - Z (Box 84)
  - 1995 Fall A - P (Box 84)
  - 1995 Fall R - Z (Box 85)
  - 1996 Spring A - P (Box 85)
  - 1996 Spring R - Z (Box 86)
- Student records for the Class of 1992, Accession 2004-A-103
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2067
  - Mr. Keisuke Hirano; Jonathan Edwards, 1988-1992 (Box 3, Folder 501)
  - WITHDRAWN, 1988-1992
  - WITHDRAWN
- Yale College student grade lists, 1996-2001; Accession 2005-A-116
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2076
  Arranged chronologically, thereunder alphabetically by department.
  - Accounting, 1996 Fall (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - African and African-American Studies, 1996 Fall (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - American Studies, 1996 Fall (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Anthropology, 1996 Fall (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Applied Math, 1996 Fall (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Applied Physics, 1996 Fall (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Archeology, 1996 Fall (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Architecture, 1996 Fall (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Art, 1996 Fall (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Astronomy, 1996 Fall (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Biology, 1996 Fall (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - British Studies, 1996 Fall (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Cell Biology, 1996 Fall (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Chemical Engineering, 1996 Fall (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Chemistry, 1996 Fall (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Child Study, 1996 Fall (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Chinese, 1996 Fall (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Classics, 1996 Fall (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Classic Civilizations, 1996 Fall (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - College Seminars, 1996 Fall (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Comparative Literature, 1996 Fall (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Computer Science, 1996 Fall (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Czech, 1996 Fall (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Divinity School, 1996 Fall (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Drama School, 1996 Fall (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Economics, 1996 Fall (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - East Asian Studies, 1996 Fall (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - EID, 1996 Fall (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Electrical Engineering, 1996 Fall (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - English, 1996 Fall (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - EPandE, 1996 Fall (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Engineering and Applied Science, 1996 Fall (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Film Studies, 1996 Fall (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Forestry and Environmental Studies, 1996 Fall (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - French, 1996 Fall (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Geology and Geophysics, 1996 Fall (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - German, 1996 Fall (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - German Studies, 1996 Fall (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Greek, 1996 Fall (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - History, 1996 Fall (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - HPA, 1996 Fall (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - History of Art, 1996 Fall (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - HsPtcs (D.S.), 1996 Fall (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - History of Science, History of Medicine, 1996 Fall (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Humanities, 1996 Fall (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Indonesian, 1996 Fall (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - IHD, 1996 Fall (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - International Studies, 1996 Fall (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Italian, 1996 Fall (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Japanese, 1996 Fall (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Judaic Studies, 1996 Fall (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Korean, 1996 Fall (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Latin, 1996 Fall (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Latin American Studies, 1996 Fall (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Linguistics, 1996 Fall (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Literature, 1996 Fall (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Literature (D.S.), 1996 Fall (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Management, 1996 Fall (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Math, 1996 Fall (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Mechanical Engineering, 1996 Fall (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - MIC, 1996 Fall (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - MPA, 1996 Fall (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - MBandB, 1996 Fall (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Music, 1996 Fall (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Music School, 1996 Fall (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Near East, 1996 Fall (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Organismal Biology, 1996 Fall (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Operations Research, 1996 Fall (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Philosophy, 1996 Fall (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Philosophy (D.S.), 1996 Fall (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Physics, 1996 Fall (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - Polish, 1996 Fall (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - Political Science, 1996 Fall (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - Portuguese, 1996 Fall (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - Psychology, 1996 Fall (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - PPM, 1996 Fall (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - Religious Studies, 1996 Fall (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - Russian and E.E., 1996 Fall (Box 1, Folder 78)
  - Russian, 1996 Fall (Box 1, Folder 79)
  - Science, 1996 Fall (Box 1, Folder 80)
  - Sociology, 1996 Fall (Box 1, Folder 81)
  - Spanish, 1996 Fall (Box 1, Folder 82)
  - Statistics, 1996 Fall (Box 1, Folder 83)
  - Studies of the Environment, 1996 Fall (Box 1, Folder 84)
  - Study of the City, 1996 Fall (Box 1, Folder 85)
  - Teacher Prep, 1996 Fall (Box 1, Folder 86)
  - Theater Studies, 1996 Fall (Box 1, Folder 87)
  - Ukraine, 1996 Fall (Box 1, Folder 88)
  - Women's Studies, 1996 Fall (Box 1, Folder 89)
  - Accounting, 1997 Fall (Box 2, Folder 90)
  - African and African-American Studies, 1997 Fall (Box 2, Folder 91)
  - American Studies, 1997 Fall (Box 2, Folder 92)
  - Anthropology, 1997 Fall (Box 2, Folder 93)
  - Applied Math, 1997 Fall (Box 2, Folder 94)
  - Applied Physics, 1997 Fall (Box 2, Folder 95)
  - Archeology, 1997 Fall (Box 2, Folder 96)
  - Architecture, 1997 Fall (Box 2, Folder 97)
  - Art, 1997 Fall (Box 2, Folder 98)
  - Astronomy, 1997 Fall (Box 2, Folder 99)
  - Biology, 1997 Fall (Box 2, Folder 100)
  - Biomedical Engineering, 1997 Fall (Box 2, Folder 101)
  - British Studies, 1997 Fall (Box 2, Folder 102)
  - Cell Biology, 1997 Fall (Box 2, Folder 103)
  - Chemical Engineering, 1997 Fall (Box 2, Folder 104)
  - Chemistry, 1997 Fall (Box 2, Folder 105)
  - Child Study, 1997 Fall (Box 2, Folder 106)
  - Chinese, 1997 Fall (Box 2, Folder 107)
  - Classics, 1997 Fall (Box 2, Folder 108)
  - Classic Civilizations, 1997 Fall (Box 2, Folder 109)
  - College Seminars, 1997 Fall (Box 2, Folder 110)
  - Comparative Literature, 1997 Fall (Box 2, Folder 111)
  - Computer Science, 1997 Fall (Box 2, Folder 112)
  - Czech, 1997 Fall (Box 2, Folder 113)
  - Divinity School, 1997 Fall (Box 2, Folder 114)
  - Drama School, 1997 Fall (Box 2, Folder 115)
  - Economics, 1997 Fall (Box 2, Folder 116)
  - East Asian Studies, 1997 Fall (Box 2, Folder 117)
  - Electrical Engineering, 1997 Fall (Box 2, Folder 118)
  - EMD, 1997 Fall (Box 2, Folder 119)
  - English, 1997 Fall (Box 2, Folder 120)
  - EPandE, 1997 Fall (Box 2, Folder 121)
  - Engineering and Applied Science, 1997 Fall (Box 2, Folder 122)
  - Film Studies, 1997 Fall (Box 2, Folder 123)
  - Forestry and Environmental Studies, 1997 Fall (Box 2, Folder 124)
  - French, 1997 Fall (Box 2, Folder 125)
  - Geology and Geophysics, 1997 Fall (Box 2, Folder 126)
  - German, 1997 Fall (Box 2, Folder 127)
  - German Studies, 1997 Fall (Box 2, Folder 128)
  - Greek, 1997 Fall (Box 2, Folder 129)
  - History, 1997 Fall (Box 2, Folder 130)
  - HPA, 1997 Fall (Box 2, Folder 131)
  - History of Art, 1997 Fall (Box 2, Folder 132)
  - HsPltcs (D.S.), 1997 Fall (Box 2, Folder 133)
  - History of Science, History of Medicine, 1997 Fall (Box 2, Folder 134)
  - Humanities, 1997 Fall (Box 2, Folder 135)
  - IHD, 1997 Fall (Box 2, Folder 136)
  - Indonesian, 1997 Fall (Box 2, Folder 137)
  - International Studies, 1997 Fall (Box 2, Folder 138)
  - Italian, 1997 Fall (Box 2, Folder 139)
  - Japanese, 1997 Fall (Box 2, Folder 140)
  - Judaic Studies, 1997 Fall (Box 2, Folder 141)
  - Korean, 1997 Fall (Box 2, Folder 142)
  - Latin, 1997 Fall (Box 2, Folder 143)
  - Latin American Studies, 1997 Fall (Box 2, Folder 144)
  - Law School, 1997 Fall (Box 2, Folder 145)
  - Linguistics, 1997 Fall (Box 2, Folder 146)
  - Literature, 1997 Fall (Box 2, Folder 147)
  - Literature (D.S.), 1997 Fall (Box 2, Folder 148)
  - Math, 1997 Fall (Box 2, Folder 149)
  - Mechanical Engineering, 1997 Fall (Box 2, Folder 150)
  - MBandB, 1997 Fall (Box 2, Folder 151)
  - Music, 1997 Fall (Box 2, Folder 152)
  - Music School, 1997 Fall (Box 2, Folder 153)
  - Near East, 1997 Fall (Box 2, Folder 154)
  - Operations Research, 1997 Fall (Box 2, Folder 155)
  - Philosophy, 1997 Fall (Box 2, Folder 156)
  - Philosophy (D.S.), 1997 Fall (Box 2, Folder 157)
  - Physics, 1997 Fall (Box 2, Folder 158)
  - Polish, 1997 Fall (Box 2, Folder 159)
  - Political Science, 1997 Fall (Box 2, Folder 160)
  - Portuguese, 1997 Fall (Box 2, Folder 161)
  - Psychology, 1997 Fall (Box 2, Folder 162)
  - PPM, 1997 Fall (Box 2, Folder 163)
  - Religious Studies, 1997 Fall (Box 2, Folder 164)
  - Russian and E.E., 1997 Fall (Box 2, Folder 165)
  - Russian, 1997 Fall (Box 2, Folder 166)
  - Slavic, 1997 Fall (Box 2, Folder 167)
  - Sociology, 1997 Fall (Box 2, Folder 168)
  - Spanish, 1997 Fall (Box 2, Folder 169)
  - Statistics, 1997 Fall (Box 2, Folder 170)
  - Studies of the Environment, 1997 Fall (Box 2, Folder 171)
  - Teacher Prep, 1997 Fall (Box 2, Folder 172)
  - Theater Studies, 1997 Fall (Box 2, Folder 173)
  - Ukraine, 1997 Fall (Box 2, Folder 174)
  - Women's Studies, 1997 Fall (Box 2, Folder 175)
  - Accounting, 1998 Fall (Box 3, Folder 176)
  - African Studies, 1998 Fall (Box 3, Folder 177)
  - African and Afro-American Studies, 1998 Fall (Box 3, Folder 178)
  - American Studies, 1998 Fall (Box 3, Folder 179)
  - Anthropology, 1998 Fall (Box 3, Folder 180)
  - Applied Math, 1998 Fall (Box 3, Folder 181)
  - Applied Physics, 1998 Fall (Box 3, Folder 182)
  - Archeology, 1998 Fall (Box 3, Folder 183)
  - Art, 1998 Fall (Box 3, Folder 184)
  - Astronomy, 1998 Fall (Box 3, Folder 185)
  - Biology, 1998 Fall (Box 3, Folder 186)
  - Biomedical Engineering, 1998 Fall (Box 3, Folder 187)
  - British Studies, 1998 Fall (Box 3, Folder 188)
  - Cell Biology, 1998 Fall (Box 3, Folder 189)
  - Chemical Engineering, 1998 Fall (Box 3, Folder 190)
  - Chemistry, 1998 Fall (Box 3, Folder 191)
  - Child Study, 1998 Fall (Box 3, Folder 192)
  - Chinese, 1998 Fall (Box 3, Folder 193)
  - Classics, 1998 Fall (Box 3, Folder 194)
  - Classic Civilizations, 1998 Fall (Box 3, Folder 195)
  - College Seminars, 1998 Fall (Box 3, Folder 196)
  - Comparative Literature, 1998 Fall (Box 3, Folder 197)
  - Computer Science, 1998 Fall (Box 3, Folder 198)
  - Czech, 1998 Fall (Box 3, Folder 199)
  - Divinity School, 1998 Fall (Box 3, Folder 200)
  - Drama School, 1998 Fall (Box 3, Folder 201)
  - East Asian Studies, 1998 Fall (Box 3, Folder 202)
  - Economics, 1998 Fall (Box 3, Folder 203)
  - Ecology and Evolutionary Biology, 1998 Fall (Box 3, Folder 204)
  - Electrical Engineering, 1998 Fall (Box 3, Folder 205)
  - EMD, 1998 Fall (Box 3, Folder 206)
  - English, 1998 Fall (Box 3, Folder 207)
  - EPandE, 1998 Fall (Box 3, Folder 208)
  - Ethnicity, Race andMigration, 1998 Fall (Box 3, Folder 209)
  - Engineering and Applied Science, 1998 Fall (Box 3, Folder 210)
  - Film Studies, 1998 Fall (Box 3, Folder 211)
  - Forestry and Environmental Studies, 1998 Fall (Box 3, Folder 212)
  - French, 1998 Fall (Box 3, Folder 213)
  - Geology and Geophysics, 1998 Fall (Box 3, Folder 214)
  - Genetics, 1998 Fall (Box 3, Folder 215)
  - German, 1998 Fall (Box 3, Folder 216)
  - German Spec, 1998 Fall (Box 3, Folder 217)
  - German Studies, 1998 Fall (Box 3, Folder 218)
  - Greek, 1998 Fall (Box 3, Folder 219)
  - History, 1998 Fall (Box 3, Folder 220)
  - History of Art, 1998 Fall (Box 3, Folder 221)
  - HPA, 1998 Fall (Box 3, Folder 222)
  - HsPltcs (D.S.), 1998 Fall (Box 3, Folder 223)
  - History of Science, History of Medicine, 1998 Fall (Box 3, Folder 224)
  - Humanities, 1998 Fall (Box 3, Folder 225)
  - Indonensian, 1998 Fall (Box 3, Folder 226)
  - International Studies, 1998 Fall (Box 3, Folder 227)
  - Italian, 1998 Fall (Box 3, Folder 228)
  - Japanese, 1998 Fall (Box 3, Folder 229)
  - Korean, 1998 Fall (Box 3, Folder 230)
  - Latin, 1998 Fall (Box 3, Folder 231)
  - Latin American Studies, 1998 Fall (Box 3, Folder 232)
  - Law School, 1998 Fall (Box 3, Folder 233)
  - Linguistics, 1998 Fall (Box 3, Folder 234)
  - Literature, 1998 Fall (Box 3, Folder 235)
  - Literature (D.S.), 1998 Fall (Box 3, Folder 236)
  - Management (School of), 1998 Fall (Box 3, Folder 237)
  - Math, 1998 Fall (Box 3, Folder 238)
  - Mechanical Engineering, 1998 Fall (Box 3, Folder 239)
  - MBandB, 1998 Fall (Box 3, Folder 240)
  - MCDB, 1998 Fall (Box 3, Folder 241)
  - Music, 1998 Fall (Box 3, Folder 242)
  - Music School, 1998 Fall (Box 3, Folder 243)
  - Near East, 1998 Fall (Box 3, Folder 244)
  - NR Science, 1998 Fall (Box 3, Folder 245)
  - Operations Research, 1998 Fall (Box 3, Folder 246)
  - Philosophy, 1998 Fall (Box 3, Folder 247)
  - Philosophy (D.S.), 1998 Fall (Box 3, Folder 248)
  - Physics, 1998 Fall (Box 3, Folder 249)
  - Polish, 1998 Fall (Box 3, Folder 250)
  - Political Science, 1998 Fall (Box 3, Folder 251)
  - Portuguese, 1998 Fall (Box 3, Folder 252)
  - Psychology, 1998 Fall (Box 3, Folder 253)
  - Religious Studies, 1998 Fall (Box 3, Folder 254)
  - Renaissance, 1998 Fall (Box 3, Folder 255)
  - Russian and E.E., 1998 Fall (Box 3, Folder 256)
  - Russian, 1998 Fall (Box 3, Folder 257)
  - Science, 1998 Fall (Box 3, Folder 258)
  - Slavic Lang and Lit, 1998 Fall (Box 3, Folder 259)
  - Sociology, 1998 Fall (Box 3, Folder 260)
  - Spanish, 1998 Fall (Box 3, Folder 261)
  - Special Divisional, 1998 Fall (Box 3, Folder 262)
  - Statistics, 1998 Fall (Box 3, Folder 263)
  - Study of the City, 1998 Fall (Box 3, Folder 264)
  - Studies of the Environment, 1998 Fall (Box 3, Folder 265)
  - Teacher Prep, 1998 Fall (Box 3, Folder 266)
  - Theater Studies, 1998 Fall (Box 3, Folder 267)
  - Ukraine, 1998 Fall (Box 3, Folder 268)
  - Women's Studies, 1998 Fall (Box 3, Folder 269)
  - Accounting, 1999 Fall (Box 4, Folder 270)
  - African Studies, 1999 Fall (Box 4, Folder 271)
  - African and Afro-American Studies, 1999 Fall (Box 4, Folder 272)
  - American Studies, 1999 Fall (Box 4, Folder 273)
  - Anthropology, 1999 Fall (Box 4, Folder 274)
  - Applied Math, 1999 Fall (Box 4, Folder 275)
  - Applied Physics, 1999 Fall (Box 4, Folder 276)
  - Archaeology, 1999 Fall (Box 4, Folder 277)
  - Architecture, 1999 Fall (Box 4, Folder 278)
  - Art, 1999 Fall (Box 4, Folder 279)
  - Astronomy, 1999 Fall (Box 4, Folder 280)
  - Biomedical Engineering, 1999 Fall (Box 4, Folder 281)
  - British Studies, 1999 Fall (Box 4, Folder 282)
  - Cell Biology, 1999 Fall (Box 4, Folder 283)
  - Chemical Engineering, 1999 Fall (Box 4, Folder 284)
  - Chemistry, 1999 Fall (Box 4, Folder 285)
  - Child Study, 1999 Fall (Box 4, Folder 286)
  - Chinese, 1999 Fall (Box 4, Folder 287)
  - Classics, 1999 Fall (Box 4, Folder 288)
  - Classic Civilizations, 1999 Fall (Box 4, Folder 289)
  - College Seminars, 1999 Fall (Box 4, Folder 290)
  - Comparative Literature, 1999 Fall (Box 4, Folder 291)
  - Computer Science, 1999 Fall (Box 4, Folder 292)
  - DeVane, 1999 Fall (Box 4, Folder 293)
  - Drama School, 1999 Fall (Box 4, Folder 294)
  - East Asian Studies, 1999 Fall (Box 4, Folder 295)
  - Ecology and Evolutionary Biology, 1999 Fall (Box 4, Folder 296)
  - Economics, 1999 Fall (Box 4, Folder 297)
  - Electrical Engineering, 1999 Fall (Box 4, Folder 298)
  - Ethics Politics and Economics, 1999 Fall (Box 4, Folder 299)
  - English, 1999 Fall (Box 4, Folder 300)
  - EMD, 1999 Fall (Box 4, Folder 301)
  - Engineering and Applied Science, 1999 Fall (Box 4, Folder 302)
  - Epidemiology and Public Health, 1999 Fall (Box 4, Folder 303)
  - Ethnicity Race and Migration, 1999 Fall (Box 4, Folder 304)
  - Film Studies, 1999 Fall (Box 4, Folder 305)
  - Forestry and Environmental Studies, 1999 Fall (Box 4, Folder 306)
  - French, 1999 Fall (Box 4, Folder 307)
  - Genetics, 1999 Fall (Box 4, Folder 308)
  - Geology and Geophysics, 1999 Fall (Box 4, Folder 309)
  - German, 1999 Fall (Box 4, Folder 310)
  - German Studies, 1999 Fall (Box 4, Folder 311)
  - Greek, 1999 Fall (Box 4, Folder 312)
  - History, 1999 Fall (Box 4, Folder 313)
  - History of Art, 1999 Fall (Box 4, Folder 314)
  - HsPltcs (D.S.), 1999 Fall (Box 4, Folder 315)
  - History of Science, History of Medicine, 1999 Fall (Box 4, Folder 316)
  - Humanities, 1999 Fall (Box 4, Folder 317)
  - HPA, 1999 Fall (Box 4, Folder 318)
  - Indonensian, 1999 Fall (Box 4, Folder 319)
  - International Studies, 1999 Fall (Box 4, Folder 320)
  - Italian, 1999 Fall (Box 4, Folder 321)
  - Japanese, 1999 Fall (Box 4, Folder 322)
  - Korean, 1999 Fall (Box 4, Folder 323)
  - Latin, 1999 Fall (Box 4, Folder 324)
  - Latin American Studies, 1999 Fall (Box 4, Folder 325)
  - Law School, 1999 Fall (Box 4, Folder 326)
  - Linguistics, 1999 Fall (Box 4, Folder 327)
  - Literature, 1999 Fall (Box 4, Folder 328)
  - Literature (D.S.), 1999 Fall (Box 4, Folder 329)
  - Management, 1999 Fall (Box 4, Folder 330)
  - Math, 1999 Fall (Box 4, Folder 331)
  - MCDB, 1999 Fall (Box 4, Folder 332)
  - Mechanical Engineering, 1999 Fall (Box 4, Folder 333)
  - MBandB, 1999 Fall (Box 4, Folder 334)
  - Music, 1999 Fall (Box 4, Folder 335)
  - Near East, 1999 Fall (Box 4, Folder 336)
  - Operations Research, 1999 Fall (Box 4, Folder 337)
  - Philosophy, 1999 Fall (Box 4, Folder 338)
  - Philosophy (D.S.), 1999 Fall (Box 4, Folder 339)
  - Physics, 1999 Fall (Box 4, Folder 340)
  - Polish, 1999 Fall (Box 4, Folder 341)
  - Political Science, 1999 Fall (Box 4, Folder 342)
  - Portuguese, 1999 Fall (Box 4, Folder 343)
  - Psychology, 1999 Fall (Box 4, Folder 344)
  - PPM, 1999 Fall (Box 4, Folder 345)
  - Religious Studies, 1999 Fall (Box 4, Folder 346)
  - Russian and E.E., 1999 Fall (Box 4, Folder 347)
  - Russian, 1999 Fall (Box 4, Folder 348)
  - Science, 1999 Fall (Box 4, Folder 349)
  - Slavic Lang and Lit, 1999 Fall (Box 4, Folder 350)
  - Sociology, 1999 Fall (Box 4, Folder 351)
  - Spanish, 1999 Fall (Box 4, Folder 352)
  - Special Divisional, 1999 Fall (Box 4, Folder 353)
  - Statistics, 1999 Fall (Box 4, Folder 354)
  - Study of the City, 1999 Fall (Box 4, Folder 355)
  - Studies of the Environment, 1999 Fall (Box 4, Folder 356)
  - Teacher Prep, 1999 Fall (Box 4, Folder 357)
  - Theater Studies, 1999 Fall (Box 4, Folder 358)
  - Vietnamese, 1999 Fall (Box 4, Folder 359)
  - Women's and Gender Studies, 1999 Fall (Box 4, Folder 360)
  - Accounting, 2000 Fall (Box 5, Folder 361)
  - African Studies, 2000 Fall (Box 5, Folder 362)
  - African-American Studies, 2000 Fall (Box 5, Folder 363)
  - American Studies, 2000 Fall (Box 5, Folder 364)
  - Anthropology, 2000 Fall (Box 5, Folder 365)
  - Applied Math, 2000 Fall (Box 5, Folder 366)
  - Applied Physics, 2000 Fall (Box 5, Folder 367)
  - Archaeological Studies, 2000 Fall (Box 5, Folder 368)
  - Architecture, 2000 Fall (Box 5, Folder 369)
  - Art, 2000 Fall (Box 5, Folder 370)
  - Astronomy, 2000 Fall (Box 5, Folder 371)
  - Biomedical Engineering, 2000 Fall (Box 5, Folder 372)
  - British Studies, 2000 Fall (Box 5, Folder 373)
  - Cell Biology, 2000 Fall (Box 5, Folder 374)
  - Chemical Engineering, 2000 Fall (Box 5, Folder 375)
  - Chemistry, 2000 Fall (Box 5, Folder 376)
  - Child Study, 2000 Fall (Box 5, Folder 377)
  - Chinese, 2000 Fall (Box 5, Folder 378)
  - Classics, 2000 Fall (Box 5, Folder 379)
  - Classic Civilizations, 2000 Fall (Box 5, Folder 380)
  - Cognitive Science, 2000 Fall (Box 5, Folder 381)
  - College Seminars, 2000 Fall (Box 5, Folder 382)
  - Comparative Literature, 2000 Fall (Box 5, Folder 383)
  - Computer Science, 2000 Fall (Box 5, Folder 384)
  - Czech, 2000 Fall (Box 5, Folder 385)
  - Drama School, 2000 Fall (Box 5, Folder 386)
  - East Asian Studies, 2000 Fall (Box 5, Folder 387)
  - Ecology and Evolutionary Biology, 2000 Fall (Box 5, Folder 388)
  - Economics, 2000 Fall (Box 5, Folder 389)
  - Electrical Engineering, 2000 Fall (Box 5, Folder 390)
  - Engineering and Applied Science, 2000 Fall (Box 5, Folder 391)
  - English, 2000 Fall (Box 5, Folder 392)
  - Environmental Engineering, 2000 Fall (Box 5, Folder 393)
  - Ethics Politics and Economics, 2000 Fall (Box 5, Folder 394)
  - Epidemiology and Public Health, 2000 Fall (Box 5, Folder 395)
  - Ethnicity Race and Migration, 2000 Fall (Box 5, Folder 396)
  - Film Studies, 2000 Fall (Box 5, Folder 397)
  - Forestry and Environmental Studies, 2000 Fall (Box 5, Folder 398)
  - French, 2000 Fall (Box 5, Folder 399)
  - Geology and Geophysics, 2000 Fall (Box 5, Folder 400)
  - German, 2000 Fall (Box 5, Folder 401)
  - German Studies, 2000 Fall (Box 5, Folder 402)
  - Greek, 2000 Fall (Box 5, Folder 403)
  - Hindi, 2000 Fall (Box 5, Folder 404)
  - History, 2000 Fall (Box 5, Folder 405)
  - History of Art, 2000 Fall (Box 5, Folder 406)
  - HsPltcs (D.S.), 2000 Fall (Box 5, Folder 407)
  - History of Science, History of Medicine, 2000 Fall (Box 5, Folder 408)
  - Humanities, 2000 Fall (Box 5, Folder 409)
  - HPA, 2000 Fall (Box 5, Folder 410)
  - International Studies, 2000 Fall (Box 5, Folder 411)
  - Italian, 2000 Fall (Box 5, Folder 412)
  - Japanese, 2000 Fall (Box 5, Folder 413)
  - Judaic Studies, 2000 Fall (Box 5, Folder 414)
  - Korean, 2000 Fall (Box 5, Folder 415)
  - Latin, 2000 Fall (Box 5, Folder 416)
  - Latin American Studies, 2000 Fall (Box 5, Folder 417)
  - Law School, 2000 Fall (Box 5, Folder 418)
  - Linguistics, 2000 Fall (Box 5, Folder 419)
  - Literature, 2000 Fall (Box 5, Folder 420)
  - Literature (D.S.), 2000 Fall (Box 5, Folder 421)
  - Management, 2000 Fall (Box 5, Folder 422)
  - Math, 2000 Fall (Box 5, Folder 423)
  - MCDB, 2000 Fall (Box 5, Folder 424)
  - Mechanical Engineering, 2000 Fall (Box 5, Folder 425)
  - MBandB, 2000 Fall (Box 5, Folder 426)
  - Music, 2000 Fall (Box 5, Folder 427)
  - Music School, 2000 Fall (Box 5, Folder 428)
  - Near East Languages, 2000 Fall (Box 5, Folder 429)
  - Near East Studies, 2000 Fall (Box 5, Folder 430)
  - Neuroscience, 2000 Fall (Box 5, Folder 431)
  - Operations Research, 2000 Fall (Box 5, Folder 432)
  - Philosophy, 2000 Fall (Box 5, Folder 433)
  - Philosophy (D.S.), 2000 Fall (Box 5, Folder 434)
  - Physics, 2000 Fall (Box 5, Folder 435)
  - Polish, 2000 Fall (Box 5, Folder 436)
  - Political Science, 2000 Fall (Box 5, Folder 437)
  - Portuguese, 2000 Fall (Box 5, Folder 438)
  - Psychology, 2000 Fall (Box 5, Folder 439)
  - Religious Studies, 2000 Fall (Box 5, Folder 440)
  - Russian and E.E., 2000 Fall (Box 5, Folder 441)
  - Russian, 2000 Fall (Box 5, Folder 442)
  - Serbo-Croatian, 2000 Fall (Box 5, Folder 443)
  - Science, 2000 Fall (Box 5, Folder 444)
  - Slavic Lang and Lit, 2000 Fall (Box 5, Folder 445)
  - Sociology, 2000 Fall (Box 5, Folder 446)
  - Spanish, 2000 Fall (Box 5, Folder 447)
  - Special Divisional, 2000 Fall (Box 5, Folder 448)
  - Statistics, 2000 Fall (Box 5, Folder 449)
  - Studies of the Environment, 2000 Fall (Box 5, Folder 450)
  - Teacher Prep, 2000 Fall (Box 5, Folder 451)
  - Theater Studies, 2000 Fall (Box 5, Folder 452)
  - Ukranian, 2000 Fall (Box 5, Folder 453)
  - Vietnamese, 2000 Fall (Box 5, Folder 454)
  - Women's and Gender Studies, 2000 Fall (Box 5, Folder 455)
  - African and African-American Studies, 1997 Spring (Box 6, Folder 456)
  - American Studies, 1997 Spring (Box 6, Folder 457)
  - Anthropology, 1997 Spring (Box 6, Folder 458)
  - Anthro Spec, 1997 Spring (Box 6, Folder 459)
  - Applied Math, 1997 Spring (Box 6, Folder 460)
  - Applied Physics, 1997 Spring (Box 6, Folder 461)
  - Archeology, 1997 Spring (Box 6, Folder 462)
  - Architecture, 1997 Spring (Box 6, Folder 463)
  - Art, 1997 Spring (Box 6, Folder 464)
  - Astronomy, 1997 Spring (Box 6, Folder 465)
  - Biology, 1997 Spring (Box 6, Folder 466)
  - British Studies, 1997 Spring (Box 6, Folder 467)
  - Cell Biology, 1997 Spring (Box 6, Folder 468)
  - Chemical Engineering, 1997 Spring (Box 6, Folder 469)
  - Chemistry, 1997 Spring (Box 6, Folder 470)